<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>golang on Wizguild</title>
    <link>https://wizguild.com/tags/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in golang on Wizguild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 07:53:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wizguild.com/tags/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static Site</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/hugo-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 07:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/hugo-static-site/</guid>
      <description>I had WordPress for a myriad of years – it feels like. As my daily work involves moving clients away to other, less feature rich but more integrated solutions it became more and more pressing to check options for myself.
Hugo is written in Go, a language that I chose to implement several big projects. Accidentally, Hugo became an inspiration and source for documentation when I started to look for good articles about Go&amp;rsquo;s templating language that we use extensively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New tool: gwget, wget based on file list, downloading only missing files</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-tool-gwget-wget-based-file-list-downloading-missing-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-tool-gwget-wget-based-file-list-downloading-missing-files/</guid>
      <description>I had to pull only missing images from media folder of live to a staging server. Best way to do it was to &amp;#8230; create a tool that does exactly what I had to do.
http://github.com/shoobyban/gwget is the result. Enjoy.
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go 1.10 party waitlist</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/go-1-10-party-waitlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 07:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/go-1-10-party-waitlist/</guid>
      <description>Go 1.10 is not full of new features. But one feature makes me really happy, GOPATH being optional. I will be able to work in my projects folder (my hope, anyway).
I&amp;rsquo;m a member of the Go London User Group, although I have never managed to either turn up or get in yet. I wander if Gophers are as nice people as my e-commerce peeps.
Oh by the way, I love math.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang experiments, Data Transformation</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/golang-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/golang-experiments/</guid>
      <description>Wow, two years without (published) post!
I&amp;#8217;ve started to experiment with Go in the meantime. I have to admit I&amp;#8217;m far from being able to write good code in Go, not that I could tell this from any other programming languages, but hey, it&amp;#8217;s something.
As my normal day job involves some backend here and there and we are doing some serious ETL magic, I had to look around for a transformation language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>