<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wizguild</title>
    <link>https://wizguild.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wizguild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 07:53:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wizguild.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Static Site</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/hugo-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 07:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/hugo-static-site/</guid>
      <description>I had WordPress for a myriad of years – it feels like. As my daily work involves moving clients away to other, less feature rich but more integrated solutions it became more and more pressing to check options for myself.
Hugo is written in Go, a language that I chose to implement several big projects. Accidentally, Hugo became an inspiration and source for documentation when I started to look for good articles about Go&amp;rsquo;s templating language that we use extensively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New tool: gwget, wget based on file list, downloading only missing files</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-tool-gwget-wget-based-file-list-downloading-missing-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-tool-gwget-wget-based-file-list-downloading-missing-files/</guid>
      <description>I had to pull only missing images from media folder of live to a staging server. Best way to do it was to &amp;#8230; create a tool that does exactly what I had to do.
http://github.com/shoobyban/gwget is the result. Enjoy.
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go 1.10 party waitlist</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/go-1-10-party-waitlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 07:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/go-1-10-party-waitlist/</guid>
      <description>Go 1.10 is not full of new features. But one feature makes me really happy, GOPATH being optional. I will be able to work in my projects folder (my hope, anyway).
I&amp;rsquo;m a member of the Go London User Group, although I have never managed to either turn up or get in yet. I wander if Gophers are as nice people as my e-commerce peeps.
Oh by the way, I love math.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang experiments, Data Transformation</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/golang-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/golang-experiments/</guid>
      <description>Wow, two years without (published) post!
I&amp;#8217;ve started to experiment with Go in the meantime. I have to admit I&amp;#8217;m far from being able to write good code in Go, not that I could tell this from any other programming languages, but hey, it&amp;#8217;s something.
As my normal day job involves some backend here and there and we are doing some serious ETL magic, I had to look around for a transformation language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another watchface</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/another-watchface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 21:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/another-watchface/</guid>
      <description>I have to say creating beautiful watchfaces is addictive. I had to create a new one, now a replica. I&amp;#8217;ve found a Gucci watch I would love to have – but as a smartwatch. Creating it was fun, having it pure joy. See watchfaces page for details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watchface for Pebble published</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/pebble-watchface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 15:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/pebble-watchface/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve published my latest watchface, ShoMaurice, after using Maurice for a while and missing/disliking few things about it. I can&amp;#8217;t help it. Pebble&amp;#8217;s decision to make C the primary language for developing watchfaces was an excellent choice. Of course you can theoretically make apps in JavaScript but why?
I have other projects as well but I enjoy this, with a few hours of coding I create something beautiful, then I carry it with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pebble Smartwatch</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/pebble-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 16:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/pebble-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Pebble smartwatch projects ShoOne A simple watchface ShoOne watchface for Pebble Smartwatch.

This watchface is tailored to my taste. Analog watch with no second handle, rounded and distinguishable minute and hour handles, day of the week, day of the month, bluetooth connection vibration alert and display, battery and battery percentage, digital time display on the bottom, 3 and 9 o&amp;#8217;clock digits for readability, so everything I need. Probably everything you will need and like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PIM weekend update</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/pim-weekend-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 21:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/pim-weekend-update/</guid>
      <description>Rewriting software is good. Code katas are good. Painful but good. Implementing the PIM on one platform and reimplementing it on a different one is especially painful.
Implementing API instead of direct database connection feels nice though.
As well as having an established framework like Symfony2. I had no real problem with the other one but when I will have to support it longer than the support will be available for the framework, sounds like a good idea to just switch – and learn everything again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PIM updates</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/pim-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 21:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/pim-updates/</guid>
      <description>In the past few weeks I have been working on the PIM (Product Management System) for my Magento instance. With the current setup we can work on the products without having to touch Magento admin.
Product data is versioned and synchronised both ways on every PIM product list display – this is not optimal but works well, I will probably create a cron job.
Attributes and attribute sets are also synchronised, CRUD is ready but I don&amp;#8217;t want to show it on the frontend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Product Information Management system for Magento</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/simple-pim-for-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 07:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/simple-pim-for-magento/</guid>
      <description>Product Information Management systems help you to manage product information centrally. In a sense Magento is a PIM.
Magento doesn&amp;#8217;t allow you to have versioned product data. In most cases this is not a problem, because you want to sell based on the latest information and you have a reliable content management team. But what if this is not the case, you have computer illiterate shop assistants or old people trying to manage the site?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bee-Bot and Sphero magic is coming</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/bee-bot-and-sphero-magic-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 10:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/bee-bot-and-sphero-magic-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>We have a new pet at home – a Sphero. Kids love it but most of the programming tools are not for 5 years olds. With the help of old turtle logic and their recent experience playing with Bee-Bots in school we had some fun already. Keep your eyes open, BeeSphero is coming!
[Update 30/04/2014] Bee support didn&amp;#8217;t react to my support request yet (Apple needs their approval too), I suppose they are busy developing the other bots&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year ’13</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/year-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 10:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/year-13/</guid>
      <description>This is the time of the year when I do my little stock-taking around my memories about last year.
Mate had a good start in the school with the exception of some innocent violence pushing and kicking others. He has a good grasp of reading, he is using this newly acquired skill with confidence. The school turned out as an excellent choice.
Daniel failed to get good GCSE grades, but we have found a course at East Surrey College for him where he seems to be happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cache warmup based on sitemap</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/cache-warmup-based-on-sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2013 09:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/cache-warmup-based-on-sitemap/</guid>
      <description>I work with multiple sites without cache warmup technology. So I created one.
Don&amp;#8217;t be mislead, it&amp;#8217;s simple.
Basic usage:
&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; $ ./warmup.rb www.someurl.tld&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; 
It will
 download http://www.someurl.tld/sitemap.xml parse that sitemap for urls run through that list of urls, downloading every HTML to warmup the cache  For further information and the code check up the Github repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iRecipebook on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-facebook-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 22:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-facebook-page/</guid>
      <description>As I&amp;#8217;m working on Facebook share &amp;#8211; there will be a share button under the recipe viewer screen that creates a Facebook note from the recipe &amp;#8211; I had to create a Facebook page so I can link to it from every post.
Please like and check iRecipebook app Facebook page, I will update TODOs, fresh screenshots, recipes and my copy-paste resource links there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting to Storyboard based design</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/converting-to-storyboard-based-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 08:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/converting-to-storyboard-based-design/</guid>
      <description>As Apple is pushing Storyboard based app development I&amp;#8217;ve decided to give it a go. Having a family holiday with lots of spare time after the pools closed I&amp;#8217;ve started to pull it together for iRecipeBook.
I had to find out how to simplify and standardise my old – I mean really old – code that I call guano code, created layer-by-layer as technology changed and requests came. Mostly it was about delegates, callbacks and properties – duplicated here and there, non-standard solutions for supporting of older (iOS 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Data iCloud support on iOS</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/core-data-icloud-support-on-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 09:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/core-data-icloud-support-on-ios/</guid>
      <description>As of today, we still have 4.x systems running, iOS 5 is still not real minority, so I can&amp;#8217;t just use iOS 6 API.
After reading several articles and trying every framework and sample code I could find my verdict is the same, iOS is not ready for Core Data iCloud yet. The currently available iOS versions are not behaving the same way so either it&amp;#8217;s a testing nightmare or just a nightmare, developers can choose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iRecipeBook in Russian and Chinese</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-in-russian-and-chinese/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 10:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-in-russian-and-chinese/</guid>
      <description>I had some time to focus on localisation. As 4.3 and 5.0 version is still majority so I can&amp;#8217;t really put iCloud features in use, I did something instead for non-English speakers. I hope every translation is correct. If not, please let me know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toddlers’ Blocks for iPad and iPhone</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/toddlers-blocks-for-ipad-and-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 11:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/toddlers-blocks-for-ipad-and-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Finally I&amp;#8217;ve released my block-building game for the kids! They&amp;#8217;ve been testing it on the iPad for ages, asking for more faces, telling me that they like this, don&amp;#8217;t like that etc.
Of course for App Store screen-shots I had to modify the UI, for loading and saving block layouts, it&amp;#8217;s hard to create the same screen-shots for all the resolutions&amp;#8230; and left a broken callback in the code even after testing, so 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toddlers&#39; Blocks - iPad and iPhone game</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/colorblocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 10:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/colorblocks/</guid>
      <description>Toddlers&amp;#8217; Blocks is a 2D block building game for toddlers and older kids up to 99 years old. No violence &amp;#8211; except of clashing blocks and downfalls &amp;#8211; no need to learn how to play it but helps to build confidence with real world physics.
There is no real goal nor rules but to have fun.
&amp;nbsp;
Update: 26/11/2015: Sorry but the app has been discontinued.
&amp;nbsp;
Support Please use this contact form to send us your comments, requests, ideas, bug reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last year of maya calendar</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/last-year-of-maya-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 20:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/last-year-of-maya-calendar/</guid>
      <description>This post is about last year.
I have to say it was really colourful. Lets begin with office matters. This was my second year at the company, we had good year so management decided to go to other markets too. This meant new language to support, having fun with French again, c&amp;#8217;est bon. New colleagues, lots of learning. Good and bad decisions, really good and really bad days too.
At home we have helping hand (au pair) so my loved one Emese has a full time job again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iRecipeBook for iPad</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-for-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 11:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-for-ipad/</guid>
      <description>We have a new release! The iPad compatible iRecipeBook was a request, actually we had a bad review, stating that the – iPhone only – iRecipeBook looks wrong on the iPad&amp;#8230; The reviewer stated that five stars will be the award of an iPad compatible release. I&amp;#8217;m waiting!
Meanwhile I&amp;#8217;m already working on localisations, social networking update (Facebook share, Twitter, Pinterest maybe&amp;#8230;) and sharing recipes via email and from within the App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New iRecipeBook release and more</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-irecipebook-release-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 11:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-irecipebook-release-and-more/</guid>
      <description>iRecipeBook released in App Store just few weeks ago but we already have news about further developments. The new release will support iPad, will have iOS usability and design improvements.
We plan to release it just before Christmas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magento</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/magento/</guid>
      <description> Magento is the most widely used e-commerce solution.
My posts about Magento technology    New tool: gwget, wget based on file list, downloading only missing files   PIM weekend update   PIM updates   Simple Product Information Management system for Magento   Cache warmup based on sitemap   Creating Magento admin grid without database tables     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Magento admin grid without database tables</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/creating-magento-admin-grid-without-database-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 13:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/creating-magento-admin-grid-without-database-tables/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s not common that you have to display something that&amp;#8217;s not in the Magento database. It was not too difficult to figure out how to do it but checking this might save you few minutes.
Feel free to download the code itself: Wizguild_VirtualGrid.zip
 Virtual grid package structure  In the Grid.php I create a Varien_Data_Collection object: protected function _prepareCollection() { $collection = new Varien_Data_Collection(); foreach (array(&#39;alpha&#39;,&#39;beta&#39;,&#39;charlie&#39;) as $item) { $data = new Varien_Object(); $data-&amp;gt;setName($item); $collection-&amp;gt;addItem($data); } $this-&amp;gt;setCollection($collection); } &amp;#8230;then just use it in the _prepareColumns():</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MageHack 2012 London</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/magehack-2012-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 08:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/magehack-2012-london/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write a blogpost about MageHack 2012 London (magehack.com) but somehow failed until now. I&amp;#8217;ll be brief as it was long ago and the memory is fading fast.
There was a pub warm-up event on the Friday before the event, with beers and schnitzel (a guy grabbed the last one just before me), sausages, mash&amp;#8230; we&amp;#8217;ve discussed our plans, trying to find out who will be possible project owner, who will join, and basically who&amp;#8217;s who.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moved domain finally</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 16:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>So here I am, finish multi-branding all say. I&amp;#8217;m now on wizguild.com, migrating everything here. First of all, my projects on the main site (mostly done, more coming) and my support sites for iOS apps. Although I have no time and intention to blog regularly I&amp;#8217;ve migrated my old stuff here for the posterity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TextWrangler PHPTidy filter</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/textwrangler_phptidy_filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 13:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/textwrangler_phptidy_filter/</guid>
      <description>I love TextWrangler. Performance of TextWrangler is just incredible compared to the alternatives. Just try to open a few hundred megabytes long XML and do a search and replace. Others will give you the spinning beach-ball for minutes. Its only real weakness is long lines. I miss few key features, though. I&amp;#8217;m not a big fan of BBedit, those extra features are not for me, I actually found them very distracting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated iRecipeBook finally</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/updated-irecipebook-finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 21:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/updated-irecipebook-finally/</guid>
      <description>It took terribly long to fix the built-in web server. Thank you for your support by using the App and sorry for annoyances. The focus is on social networking features now.
As the database is bigger and bigger, especially after uploading images for every recipe I&amp;#8217;ve realized maybe we will have to implement an option to get rid of big images. The big image feature was introduced to help social networking publication, but clearly we can&amp;#8217;t sacrifice launch performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iRecipeBook - Recipe book for iPhone, editable from web browser</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/recipebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 19:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/recipebook/</guid>
      <description>iRecipeBook |FAQ/Documentation | Feedback | Privacy Policy | Screenshots      &amp;nbsp; iRecipeBook – Recipe book for iPhone, editable from web browser   iRecipeBook is an easy to use recipe book application for your iPhone and iPod Touch with web remote editing feature. You can enable remote editing from the App, load up a web browser and freely copy-paste and edit your recipes. You can easily add lots of recipes with web based copy-paste function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iWordsmith</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/wordsmith/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 16:49:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/wordsmith/</guid>
      <description>iWordsmith |FAQ/Documentation | Feedback | Screenshots      We have folded a word into the 3&amp;#215;3 or 4&amp;#215;4 matrix, try to find it! You have to use all the letters! Test and improve your vocabulary in the most sensitive 8-16 letters range!  Update: 26/11/2015: Sorry but the app has been discontinued.      Features:   &amp;#8211; 3&amp;#215;3 challenge (8-9 letters long words)   &amp;#8211; 4&amp;#215;4 challenge (-16 letters long words)   &amp;#8211; time challenge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone/iPad (old)</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 15:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/iphone/</guid>
      <description>Our small team is publishing programs for the iPhone/iPad/iPod Touch market from inner drive. When we need a program, we code it and release it. When we need an update, we update it. Sometimes we have time to do updates by request, sometimes not. Sorry for the later, it&amp;#8217;s not because you are not important, but because we have less resources.
Update: 26/11/2015: Sorry but all apps have been discontinued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five or More</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/fom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 15:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/fom/</guid>
      <description>Five or More is an addictive game, helps you to spend as much time as you can, also good for training concentration or pointing accuracy. The game&amp;#8217;s objective is to align five or more balls of the same color causing them to disappear, as often as possible. This is the iPhone port of the game GLines, also known as Five Or More from Gnome Project.
As an early pilot project please do not blame me for the awkwardness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>twenty-eleven</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/twenty-eleven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 12:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/twenty-eleven/</guid>
      <description>Looking back on the year, as usual. My memory is so bad I have to take notes 🙂
If last year was positive, it&amp;#8217;s even better, in every aspects.
I have a nice new job in a small international company as Head of IT / Architect, some kind of a CTO but with lots of fun around the code. We have few Magento systems, building new sites regularly, working with logistics companies and other partners connecting our systems to their, providing them data, sending and updating orders etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English – Hungarian dictionary and idiom dictionary for Mac OS X spotlight</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/english-hungarian-dictionary-and-idiom-dictionary-for-mac-os-x-spotlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 11:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/english-hungarian-dictionary-and-idiom-dictionary-for-mac-os-x-spotlight/</guid>
      <description>This is an English &amp;#8211; Hungarian dictionary and English idiom &amp;#8211; Hungarian dictionary for Mac OS X spotlight. Install the unzipped files it into /Library/Dictionaries and check /Applications/Dictionary.app settings for details.
          Download: Dictionary.zip 15.29 MB</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wizguild.com – Wizards Guild</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/wizguild/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 11:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/wizguild/</guid>
      <description>We are moving domain, welcome to wizguild.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 10:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a guild of fine craftsmen from the software industry. We are not just blessed with knowledge but with kindness and openness to others&amp;#8217; problems.
Our focus is mainly Mac OS X, Go, iOS, Magento and any other PHP based development, e-commerce consulting, retail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$year=2010; $year&#43;&#43;;</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/year2010-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/year2010-year/</guid>
      <description>My first year in the UK.  I have had great time at the NSI, I have created the new patrolstore.com based on Magento, a small site called apace.org.uk for police chiefs using Zend Frameworks, 3 other sites are under testing, a new mail server and lots of small achievements. I have a new nick: they call me &amp;#8220;the Hungarian wizard&amp;#8221; 🙂  We live here in Redhill, just south of London in a nice little two bedroom rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 07:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/golang/</guid>
      <description> I use Go every day as part of my work and as hobby.
Here are my posts about Go    Hugo Static Site   New tool: gwget, wget based on file list, downloading only missing files   Go 1.10 party waitlist   Golang experiments, Data Transformation     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>=SUM(2009)</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/sum2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 09:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/sum2009/</guid>
      <description>All right, time to post all things about 2009. I cannot wait longer.
Pros:
 My son, Máté (Matthew) was born in January I have a new app in iTunes App Store: iRecipeBook Acted as &amp;#8220;Most Senior Apple Consultant&amp;#8221; for Hungary I had nice server consolidation projects at Apcom Also I had very nice in-house development projects I had no major health problems  Cons:
 Apcom is much smaller now There is a joke about recession: A recession is when your neighbour loses his job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Wok Chicken</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/my-wok-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 17:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/my-wok-chicken/</guid>
      <description>1 chicken breast 2 table spoon of olive oil 1 can of mushroom 1-2 carrot 1 table spoon of wok spice (contains salt, sugar, garlic, pepper, soy sauce, ginger, fenugreek, turmeric)&amp;#8230; I know this is cheating 😉 soy sauce 1 table spoon of starch 1 medium sized onion 100g of rice noodle water  Clean and slice the chicken to 2&amp;#215;3 cm slices, fry them in olive oil till they are white.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/mat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2009 05:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/mat/</guid>
      <description>In few days I realised I cannot finish this post.
Update: My son Matthew turned 9 months few days ago. He is clever and as handsome as me 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training on a Nikon D40</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/training-on-a-nikon-d40/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 18:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/training-on-a-nikon-d40/</guid>
      <description>Tough DSLRs are not for those who cannot make a steady shot with a pocket cam I decided to buy a D40 after recognising that my pictures are full of noise.
The challenge: to learn to shoot nice photos. I&amp;#8217;ve read tutorials, books about the subject, I know the basics, the theory, but this is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>year&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 20:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/year/</guid>
      <description>Some key events in 2008:
 learnt the basics of the French language spent few nice days in Paris again 🙂 fruitful vacation in Döbrönte &amp;#8230; see last entry 😉 I organized the first Apple summer camp and an educational week became Zyxel switch specialist and Apple Certified Technical Coordinator Emese is pregnant with my son 😀  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five or More is in App Store</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/five-or-more-is-in-app-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 07:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/five-or-more-is-in-app-store/</guid>
      <description>Hurray, hurray and hurray. My little game is in the App Store! It took long, but it&amp;#8217;s there. You can download it for free of course, search for &amp;#8220;Shooby&amp;#8221;. I hope you will find it as annoying and fun as I do.
Update: I have been reviewed by &amp;#8220;whoneedsaname&amp;#8221;. It&amp;#8217;s fascinating how the guy writes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can’t wait to publish my iPhone apps</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/cant-wait-to-publish-my-iphone-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 15:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/cant-wait-to-publish-my-iphone-apps/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Five Or More game screenshot
I&amp;#8217;m still waiting Apple&amp;#8217;s approval of my request to join their developer community. It&amp;#8217;s not straightforward, because I cannot buy anything from Apple Store. I live on the wrong side of the world. I had to fax them papers to prove I will buy the subscription, now they are sitting on this paper and ask me to wait.
It&amp;#8217;s not so easy to wait, after waiting more than one year to release something it&amp;#8217;s more than annoying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evening</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/evening/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 19:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/evening/</guid>
      <description>I like to walk home with Emese, chatting about the day and whatching the nature around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>periodic post, 0x20</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/periodic-post-0x20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/periodic-post-0x20/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m older, this is how the Universe works. And I blog this. No comment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenOffice.org 3 beta is fast!</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/openofficeorg-3-beta-is-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 08:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/openofficeorg-3-beta-is-fast/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t wait the stable release! After years of watching the splash screen I was delighted to see how fast is the new OOo beta. Service guys has a big XLS price-list of the service parts, this beta software opened this huge file with such an easiness and speed&amp;#8230; I will like the native OOo, I think. NeoOffice is still better if you have to edit something, I had many problems with the fonts and chart sizes, this is normal for a beta software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone SDK</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/iphone-sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 08:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/iphone-sdk/</guid>
      <description>This morning I have finished porting iLines to official SDK. Works well. I have to admit there are drawbacks (lack of Interface Builder, coming soon) but my code was also buggy (I&amp;#8217;m not surprised :))
So now I know I&amp;#8217;ll be able to write software and probably I&amp;#8217;ll do it. Before this Apple will have to release firmware 2.0 and this is the hardest thing to wait for something you can use now (theoretically).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X leopard (aka 10.5) first impressions</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/mac-os-x-leopard-aka-105-first-impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2007 18:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/mac-os-x-leopard-aka-105-first-impressions/</guid>
      <description>The new cat gives me so much, I can&amp;#8217;t count everything.
After a clean install I have moved my programs into the Applications folder, then Application Support, Preferences and many things from my old home folder. After this I had a clean leo with my apps working (or not :))
I had to squash some bugs, too, for example FileMaker works with US locale but nothing else, hot-keys stopped working with international keyboard layouts (for example command-`, move focus to next window) this is really painful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>time to celebrate</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/time-to-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2007 15:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/time-to-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Finally, the time has come. Steve Jobs announced the iPhone SDK, available from February, 2008! It&amp;#8217;s so good to be Apple fan, again 🙂 Beware of my Apps 😀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>programming is fun</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/programming-is-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 19:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/programming-is-fun/</guid>
      <description>Hell, yes. I had problem with a regexp today and I wrote a small eval() based code (3 or 4 lines) what I can use as debugger&amp;#8230; in the evening I had this crazy idea&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recently</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/months-are-flying-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 17:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/months-are-flying-fast/</guid>
      <description>About last few months in nutshell:
 moved into our flat bought a Rover 45 (1.6i club, 2003 model) iStyle Hungary (company where I work) opened 2 new shops Maji is 10 years old summer was hot, we worked much  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Skype theme</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/little-skype-style-hack-for-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/little-skype-style-hack-for-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s not official, barely legal (it&amp;#8217;s from an Adium theme) but looks good. To install: get it here and after uncompressing copy it into /Applications/Skype.app/Contents/Resources/ChatStyles/ (or find the according folder on Linux and Windows). You cannot switch the color scheme and can&amp;#8217;t show avatars, but it&amp;#8217;s cute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XKCD widget</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/xkcd-time-factorisation-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 12:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/xkcd-time-factorisation-widget/</guid>
      <description>I am mad, I know. I&amp;#8217;ve made the XKCD Time Factorisation widget for other XKCD fans from their comic strip.
I hope you will find it funny. Another useless widget on your Mac OS X Dashboard :).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ill</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/medical-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2007 20:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/medical-problems/</guid>
      <description>After 2 months of fighting with my pain and inflammation in my lung with aid of drugs like steroids and antibiotics I had to find that after I stopped to get those pills the pain and the inflammation came back.
But it&amp;#8217;s better than poisoning myself with steroids and drugs for blood pressure and so&amp;#8230; after one month of taking Medrol I had terrible headache (I mean terrible and way too long&amp;#8230; 3 weeks long without a minute stop) but it was better after I was able to stop taking it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alive</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2007 18:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/back/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s so good to be alive! Thanks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacFUSE sshfs</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/sshfs-on-mac-os-x-macfuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2007 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/sshfs-on-mac-os-x-macfuse/</guid>
      <description>Using Google&amp;#8217;s MacFUSE for some weeks, I&amp;#8217;m happy with it. It&amp;#8217;s cool to have sshfs on Mac 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPhone</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/announced-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2007 19:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/announced-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Today Apple has announced iPhone. I want one. I want to write programs to it. I want to use it, now. I think I&amp;#8217;m not alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Omszki</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/weekends-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2006 13:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/weekends-fun/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we had some fun at the lake Omszki. Vakhangya and his son asked me about having a chat, Maji has a new ball so we played football. It was fun, except Vakhangya had some problem with his blood pressure&amp;#8230;
I hope they are OK now 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heviz – honeymoon</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/choc-o-lait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2006 10:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/choc-o-lait/</guid>
      <description>This weekend we had nice weather at Heviz. I can&amp;#8217;t remember the last time when we were so happy and relaxed. Heviz is Hungary&amp;#8217;s most famous thermal lake, beautiful (with water lily) and radioactive water. I have no problem with my bones or muscles (the water is good for disabled people) but we had an invitation for 3 days.
The weather was so warm I walked on the street in t-shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/xsan-broadcasting-training-in-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2006 09:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/xsan-broadcasting-training-in-paris/</guid>
      <description>Finally I&amp;#8217;m here. I&amp;#8217;ve played with Xserves, Xserve RAIDs and fibre channel switches in the last few days, it was fun. French people are nice, the host of the training is a company is Agnosys.fr, a French Apple training company. They have good trainings as I understand their brochures. I&amp;#8217;ve learnt few new French words too and many about Apple video editing and server solutions. I love to be here 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X “cracked”</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/mac-os-x-cracked-heh-blah-blah/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2006 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/mac-os-x-cracked-heh-blah-blah/</guid>
      <description>Of course, with a buggy 3rd party driver. So it&amp;#8217;s not a real sensation, but good for the press (blooood!!! ahhhh!!!) Nonsense. Of course, the guy was smart, he had good stuff and the security hole is absolutely there&amp;#8230;
Hijacking a macbook in 60 secs with a 3rd party WiFi card</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back home</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/back-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2006 20:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/back-home/</guid>
      <description>In nutshell: Figthing cockroaches, working hard, trying to survive the hot weather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/from-ukrainia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 20:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/from-ukrainia/</guid>
      <description>Beregszasz (Beregovo), Ukraine, Dormitory of Transcarpatian Hungarian College Named After Ferenc Rakoczi II&amp;#8230; tomorrow we will give speeches on free software for teachers.
I&amp;#8217;m sitting in front of my machine, after a long trip. We had a meeting in Nyiregyhaza with the others and some pizza then in a 5 cars long convoy we started to annoy the border guards 🙂 It was a dumb situation when the Ukrainian border guard asked us (of course in Ukrainian language) about why we are waiting in a forbidden area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate to move</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/i-hate-to-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 11:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/i-hate-to-move/</guid>
      <description>I mean from one rent into another&amp;#8230; kills me. Aaaahh!!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FYI</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/fyi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 12:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/fyi/</guid>
      <description>Today we got married silently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server Club</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/server-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2006 09:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/server-club/</guid>
      <description>We will make a new event at A4 Apple Center (Andrassy street 4, Budapest) at Friday, Jun 30 about Mac OS X Server operating system and people around servers, read: system administrators.
My friends (who are exceptional professionals super pro-gurus) will be there, if you have questions or want to meet someone (for example me) please come. I mean you are welcome.
We will talk about servers, new technologies around Macs, free software projects, development, ideas, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New server</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2006 13:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-server/</guid>
      <description>So, after hard times I have another chance to express my ideas and feelings about my environment. I&amp;#8217;ve got new server! Wow, wow!
I&amp;#8217;m so happy!
Few words about last months:
 I&amp;#8217;m working at A4 Apple Center as Head of development, we are making financial systems for clients with Mac systems. I&amp;#8217;m quite happy with my squash play. I had to make myself move somehow. Unfortunately BMP has moved back to Bicske so I haven&amp;#8217;t got permanent partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/why-am-i-not-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2006 13:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/why-am-i-not-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Good question&amp;#8230; Maybe I have no spare time&amp;#8230; 🙁</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About 2005</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/about-2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 23:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/about-2005/</guid>
      <description>OK, so it&amp;#8217;s time for review last year. I&amp;#8217;m happy it&amp;#8217;s over. I hope I will like 2006 better.
 Projects:  Two major Flash-MySQL-perl based TV show game (currently in use on ATV and Duna TV) Web sites (kepvadasz.hu, A4 Apple Center, &amp;#8230;) Call Center application in Cocoa, Webkit, PHP and MySQL OpenOffice.org 2.0 Hungarian version with Hunspell for Mac OS X, aka FSF.hu build contribution in TV show called Macians (currently I feel shame because I have no time) on Fix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia 6111 and Mac OS X aka. how to sync, problem v3</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/nokia-6111-and-mac-os-x-aka-how-to-sync-problem-v3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 09:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/nokia-6111-and-mac-os-x-aka-how-to-sync-problem-v3/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I have bought a Nokia 6111. This is a good-looking Series 40 phone (sigh, no more python/c++ hacking, no more iSync)&amp;#8230;
While there is a program to sync contacts, etc (works well with 6111) called PhoneDirector from MacMedia, I had to write my own (and free) app to upload the contents of my Address Book to the phone.
Gnokii is a good choice, if you have just one contact to sync but if you have few hundred you will have to make a script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NeoOfficeJ for Java 14x</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/neoofficej-for-java-14x/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2005 16:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/neoofficej-for-java-14x/</guid>
      <description>New, faster, with fewer Java based bugs. Cool! I have to say Patric is working hard and making fantastic things around NeoOffice/J. Thanks, and please keep this process. Feel free to download the performance patch, it applies to 1.1 (downloadable from neooffice.org)&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mighty Mouse in real</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/mighty-mouse-in-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2005 07:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/mighty-mouse-in-real/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I brought home the first Mighty mouse for testing. I have to say I was right. This is an evolutionary mouse, but users will have to learn to use it. Clicking with the right, left or the middle (OK, its better to say 1,2,3 or primary etc.) button is easy if you don&amp;#8217;t think just do it. But when you see what you do (for example I lift my other fingers up) you will try to do it other ways and it does not work like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New mouse from Apple</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-mouse-from-apple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2005 20:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-mouse-from-apple/</guid>
      <description>I like Mighty Mouse! It seems usable, it&amp;#8217;s cute, Apple knows how to make a real product! It&amp;#8217;s so cute! Oh my! &amp;#8230;. I&amp;#8217;ll have problem with buttons at the right and left side, though. I hate to click accidentally. I hope I will like it when I&amp;#8217;ll got one 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still lots of staff to close</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/still-lots-of-staff-to-close/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2005 10:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/still-lots-of-staff-to-close/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow I will start another &amp;#8220;big project&amp;#8221; and I still have lots of unfinished stuff here. I will have to make agreements with my previous clients who are complaining for support (unfortunately all of them think it&amp;#8217;s free, gratis, etc&amp;#8230;)
Normally I help them as I should, but after a number of requests I start to slow down, losing interest. I know it&amp;#8217;s not the best what I can do, but they don&amp;#8217;t want to pay my time and although I really like them (not all of them, but in general) I have to do my other jobs, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great!</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/great/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2005 14:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/great/</guid>
      <description>We had great time at Mogyoród, exactly two days time. Nice weather, sweeeeeet relaxation, lazing all the day! Wohoooo!
We have spent two days at the Aquapark and it&amp;#8217;s camping, right before the Formula 1 madness.
Back to work! Brrrr&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess what!</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2005 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Guess, what will produce this small program.
#include &amp;lt;stdio.h&amp;gt; int main() { int a = 3; printf (&#34;a is: %dn&#34;,a); printf (&#34;++a + ++a: %dn&#34;, ++a + ++a ); printf (&#34;after this a is: %dn&#34;,a); int b = 3; printf (&#34;b is: %dn&#34;,b); printf (&#34;b++ + b++: %dn&#34;, b++ + b++ ); printf (&#34;after this b is: %dn&#34;,b); int c = 3; printf (&#34;c is: %dn&#34;,c); printf (&#34;c++ + ++c: %dn&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weeks in run</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/weeks-in-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 14:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/weeks-in-run/</guid>
      <description>Hard times, again. Hard to find time to stop, I feel something is missing. Maybe some holiday. While checking our schedule, we decided to have a break at next week. This is our last hope. I could just hope this will be OK for my clients and for Emese&amp;#8217;s boss.
The plan is to camp out somewhere near, for example the Aquapark near Mogyorod&amp;#8230; hmm&amp;#8230; sounds relaxing. Although I need some rest, the weather forecasts and state of my projects make me feel bad about the next week&amp;#8230; we will see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSL Courier IMAP certificate on Debian</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/ssl-courier-imap-certificate-on-debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 18:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/ssl-courier-imap-certificate-on-debian/</guid>
      <description>Easy way to create a new certificate instead of the autogenerated one which comes with &amp;#8220;apt-get install courier-imap-ssl&amp;#8221;:
 check your /etc/courier/imapd.cnf move the file /etc/courier/imapd.pem to another name or location dpkg-reconfigure courier-imap-ssl restart imapd and check if everything was ok  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthday party of Yoro</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/birthday-party-of-yoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2005 09:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/birthday-party-of-yoro/</guid>
      <description>We had great time at Győrújbarát. The weather was nice (little hot), the food was fantastic, and the most important, I met my good old friends from the college.
Happy 30th, Yoro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Map of Budapest</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/google-map-of-budapest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2005 05:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/google-map-of-budapest/</guid>
      <description>Oh, yes. We are in.
This is the World from where I am now.
Sounds cool, ha?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day with great things</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/day-with-great-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2005 12:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/day-with-great-things/</guid>
      <description>Emese&amp;#8216;s Birthday, she had a successful psychology exam (congratulations, Emese and Happy Birthday).
I&amp;#8217;m in trouble every time I have to buy presents. I want to buy her something neat, something what will make her happy. It&amp;#8217;s hard to find.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My English</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/my-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2005 11:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/my-english/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s bad, I know. I&amp;#8217;m not native, but I&amp;#8217;m working on my English. I have found a page to test my profile.
  Your Linguistic Profile:     45% General American English    30% Yankee    15% Dixie    10% Upper Midwestern    0% Midwestern    What Kind of American English Do You Speak?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think Different</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/think-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2005 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/think-different/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I had to figure out how the hack will I make the Mac OS X clients authenticate from Solaris 10 and Mac OS X server.
Netinfo is better, it&amp;#8217;s easy to make it work on Mac OS X, but hard to compile on Solaris. I have to configure NIS on the Sun and test if it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something is wrong</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/something-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2005 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/something-wrong/</guid>
      <description>I have to restart my blog because of a hard drive error. No backups, no mirror. Eeeek. Sounds terrible.
Update: I have managed to restore my blog entries from Google cache. Thanks, guys!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X and character problem</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/mac-os-x-and-character-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2004 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/mac-os-x-and-character-problem/</guid>
      <description>After replying the umpteen e-mail about Hungarian language specific (latin2)
õ and û character problem I have made a FAQ page. I describe how to solve the problem when Word and NeoOffice does not see the õ and û characters in a document comes from Windows. It&amp;#8217;s basically a problem specific documentation for FontBook, Apple&amp;#8217;s most important but not-so-well-known application.
(Update: Will have to find the document to correct the links)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice breakfast</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/nice-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2004 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/nice-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m sitting in a small but nice place called Café Créme just on the corner, near to our flat. The sandwich was fine (with chorizo), Emese had a melange (she said it was much more like melange compared to the others she had) and we are both using our own WiFi network from home, working and surfing&amp;#8230; It&amp;#8217;s a beautiful day, good start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Dog Linux 4.0 on iMac G5 combo</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/yellow-dog-linux-40-on-imac-g5-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2004 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/yellow-dog-linux-40-on-imac-g5-combo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m happy with my new iMac G5, it&amp;#8217;s fast, beautiful&amp;#8230; but. I cannot install
(without hacking) YDL on it, because YDL 4.0 installer does not recognise
its combo drive. Is this serious? 🙁 I will check it again soon but I have
no time for hacking a new install set&amp;#8230; I will have to find another ppc
distro.
(Update: I have successfully installed YDL 4.0.1)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death of my harddrive</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/death-of-my-harddrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2004 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/death-of-my-harddrive/</guid>
      <description>HDD of my little powerbook is living it&amp;#8217;s last hours. I&amp;#8217;m running the system
from my iPod because the harddrive gives terrible noises&amp;#8230; I wonder if it
will serve me more than days before the final stop. I will miss my data so
bad&amp;#8230;
(Update: in may my harddrive made its last moves&amp;#8230; RIP, old drive)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New install on my PB</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-install-on-my-pb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2004 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-install-on-my-pb/</guid>
      <description>I had to reinstall my system after more than a year of stability. I think I will have to
avoid installing third party programs and system extensions. I could just
hope my backup was complete 🙂
After the reinstall I had 35 gigs of space, holy hard drive! OK, OK. After
installing the most necessary programs and my backup data I have just 20
gigs of 40, but it&amp;#8217;s kind of interesting how many rubbish I used to store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NeoOffice 12A2 FSF.hu build</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/neooffice-11a2-fsfhu-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2004 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/neooffice-11a2-fsfhu-build/</guid>
      <description>Yes, a Hungarian NeoOfficeJ! I did it! Available from
http://ftp.fsf.hu/NeoOfficeJ, it&amp;#8217;s still in testing, but usable.
Feel free to use it, it&amp;#8217;s a free software (forums and other stuff at Trinity
BBS)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chatroom links from web pages</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/chatroom-links-from-web-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2004 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/chatroom-links-from-web-pages/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217; not so hard, you can link your favourite AIM (iChat) chat room at
your site: beszeljukmac chatroom (this is the Hungarian mac chatroom with good
traffic, it&amp;#8217;s hard to find it empty).
I hope I will find more chatroom links in the future&amp;#8230; 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successful Free Software show at Dunaujvaros</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/successful-free-software-show-at-dunaujvaros/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2004 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/successful-free-software-show-at-dunaujvaros/</guid>
      <description>I have taken some photos, reachable from
http://shooby.gnome.hu/pics/2004_10_11_dunaujvaros_fsf.hu_roadshow/.
We have
promises about video recordings of the event, I will have to write a video
cd from my presentation, it was such a success&amp;#8230; 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk at Infotrend 2004 Conference</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/talk-at-infotrend-2004-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2004 06:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/talk-at-infotrend-2004-conference/</guid>
      <description>INFOtrend is a trade fair and conference at the HUNGEXPO Budapest Fair
Center, 26-28 october 2004.
I have been invited to give a talk about Linux in the office environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FSF.hu Roadshow stops at Dunaujvaros</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/fsfhu-roadshow-stops-at-dunaujvaros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2004 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/fsfhu-roadshow-stops-at-dunaujvaros/</guid>
      <description>On monday the FSF.hu roadshow team will visit Dunaujvaros to deliver
speeches about Free Software and Open Source solutions. I will talk about
free software development tools.
Location of the event: Kerpely Antal Dormitory, Diszterem, Dunaújváros,
Semmelweis u. 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac fanatic show at FIX.tv again</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/mac-fanatic-show-at-fixtv-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2004 15:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/mac-fanatic-show-at-fixtv-again/</guid>
      <description>Weekly at Thursday, 20:00 CET (OK, OK, after 15 minutes of ads) about Apple
history, Mac OS X and Mac users and fanatics, news, rumors&amp;#8230; We will show
you our Mac 🙂
Come and join us, our iChat room will be &amp;#8220;beszeljukmac&amp;#8221; hopefully, live
stream is at mms://www.fix.tv/fixdsl (blah, WM stream, not QT)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog calendar works again</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/blog-calendar-works-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2004 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/blog-calendar-works-again/</guid>
      <description>OK, finally I had some time to fix a bug in the dateFilter checking code&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making custom AFP shares</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/making-custom-afp-shares/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2004 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/making-custom-afp-shares/</guid>
      <description>I hate to make temporary users and set passwords. I have made a small shell
script to help me making custom AFP shares. How to use it (from Terminal):
$ mkafpshare.sh sharename /path/of/directory/to/share
You will have to type in an administrator password (script uses sudo), then
turn off and on Personal File Sharing in System Preferences/Sharing.
When you are connecting to your mac from another mac, choose guest, and
voilà, new share 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NeoOffice 11 alpha</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/neooffice-11-alpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2004 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/neooffice-11-alpha/</guid>
      <description>Oh yes! It&amp;#8217;s incredible! I have NeoOffice based on OpenOffice 1.1 code,
thanks to Patrik. Direct link to the news entry. Knows Hungarian umlaut
characters, faster, able to save PDF, etc&amp;#8230;
By the way, I managed to make the Hungarian spell checker and hyphenation
work&amp;#8230; At home I will try to build my own Hungarian version, too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New machine on board</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-machine-on-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2004 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-machine-on-board/</guid>
      <description>After long delay (waiting for service, about 3 weeks or more) few days ago
(ok, I know, I&amp;#8217;m a bad blogger) I got my first dual processor system.
Reeeealy cute!!! A real PowerMac G4 (Gigabit Ethernet model) with two 450
MHz CPU, RAM and some other parts cannibalised from another systems. Yes, the seller have changed the hard drive to a noisy 20 gig one, my first step was to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update for anti software patent demonstration</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/update-for-anti-software-patent-demonstration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2004 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/update-for-anti-software-patent-demonstration/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m planning to join the demonstration. If you are in Hungary and you are
software developer or user you should consider to join us. Software patents
are bad.
This is one of our banners:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti software patent demonstration</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/anti-software-patent-demonstration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2004 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/anti-software-patent-demonstration/</guid>
      <description>The European Parliament will have a vote on the issue in September about
software patents. We are in the works to make that little difference by
putting pressure on the Hungarian government to withdraw their support for
the current draft.
We plan a demonstration and talks. Our last &amp;#8211; and only &amp;#8211; chance to influence
the decision to be made seems to be to put some pressure on the officials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have subversion</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/i-have-subversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2004 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/i-have-subversion/</guid>
      <description>I have been using cvs for ages. Jul is subversion fan, I wanted to try it out,
so I had to install it.
Every time I said &amp;#8220;fink install svn&amp;#8221; or &amp;#8220;fink install svn-client-ssl&amp;#8221; I got
frightened from 40 new packages (apache2 and others) so I had to find
something.
So I had to recognise I was blind&amp;#8230; on subversion&amp;#8217;s official site there is a
link to an easy installing dmg&amp;#8230; shame on me, again 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childroom destroy party</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/childroom-destroy-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2004 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/childroom-destroy-party/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#8217;ve been planning to renovate the kid&amp;#8217;s room for long time. On Sunday we
have started to remove the old wallpaper, move the furniture to other room,
etc.
Now we have a new wallpaper, and some time. Wallpaper have to dry, then we
will paint it and build the new furniture&amp;#8230; hard days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English-Hungarian dictionary on Cocoa power</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/english-hungarian-dictionary-on-cocoa-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2004 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/english-hungarian-dictionary-on-cocoa-power/</guid>
      <description>There is a new version of English-Hungarian (Angol-Magyar) dictionary at
http://egeronline.com/szotar/. I like this Cocoa application, it has nice background, it&amp;#8217;s free, fast and it can speak the English text (OK, there is no speak support for Hungarian in Mac OS X).
Good job, iJoe!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video chat with guys at the Sziget Festival</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/videochat-with-guys-at-the-sziget-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2004 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/videochat-with-guys-at-the-sziget-festival/</guid>
      <description>Scold have asked me to check for his iSight signal on the Sziget festival so
I&amp;#8217;ve seen some nice people out there. They were a bit foggy, I think they will
have to look for some way to force set the focus&amp;#8230;
On Thursday hopefully I will check them IRL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/28/</guid>
      <description>Few days ago I have grown old. I&amp;#8217;m still shocked. Nobody told me about how
it feels getting older and older every year. The cake was fine. Thanks for
all the good wishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from the CERN</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/back-from-the-cern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/back-from-the-cern/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m tired and extremely happy, I was able to see the Data Center of CERN
(European Organization for Nuclear Research, read Nuclear part as inner
particles of atoms, protons and electrons not as nuclear technology).
I have been invited by Interware Rt. (a five stars server hosting hotel)
with many young (and not so very young) IT professionals and Interware&amp;#8217;s
most important business partners.
For Your Information: The visit in CERN is for FREE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy X2</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/final-fantasy-x-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2004 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/final-fantasy-x-2/</guid>
      <description>At last, I managed to buy a FFX-2. Unfortunately, the seller did not tell me
it&amp;#8217;s a German version. We are fighting with the game. I mean I&amp;#8217;m fighting with the
German language menus, I have &amp;#8220;difficulties&amp;#8221; with German. So I will try to
find the way to exchange it to an English version. The game is fantastic, but the
new combat mechanism (aktivemodus, brrr) is too fast for me. I like to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first real camera</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/my-first-real-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2004 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/my-first-real-camera/</guid>
      <description>This week Olympus finally have shipped C-765 UZ cameras to Hungary. At last.
I have bought one, I&amp;#8217;m quite happy with it. It&amp;#8217;s a small 10X optical zoom,
4.0 megapixel digital camera with QuickTime video recording capabilities
(with sound).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Towel Day</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/our-towel-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2004 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/our-towel-day/</guid>
      <description>The day before yesterday we had excellent Towel Day. The participants were:
Jul, Szimszon, Bmp, Kecsi and me.
What is Towel Day?
Towel Day has been declared by an internet movement to celebrate Douglas
Adams&amp;#8217; memory, it is set for 25th May. The idea was that people carry
their towel with them everywhere on that day as a tribute to Doulgas Adams.
So carry your towel with you throughout the day, think about Hitchhikers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gnome 2.6</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/gnome-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2004 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/gnome-26/</guid>
      <description>Gnome 2.6 is out! I feel shame, I had no commits since the last release. I
will have to check GKB and Glines if they were working&amp;#8230; It&amp;#8217;s hard to use a
PC&amp;#8230;
I have found the missing key tab file for my ill-fated gkeycaps program, I
will try to continue the coding&amp;#8230; I have forgot to commit it into the Gnome
CVS and the program does not work without this file 😛</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folding Home</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/foldinghome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2004 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/foldinghome/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m folding proteins on my locked screen (I normally do not use any
screensaver but screen locks)&amp;#8230; Few days ago I have found (again) a protein
folding project, called Folding@Home.
The goal of the project is understand how to fold proteins and protein
aggregation, helping to fight Alzheimer&amp;#8217;s and Parkinson&amp;#8217;s disease, Mad Cow
(BSE), CJD and ALS&amp;#8230; I love to help, so I have downloaded the GUI and the
screensaver and joined to Team Mac OS X.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good changes are invisible</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/good-changes-are-invisible/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2004 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/good-changes-are-invisible/</guid>
      <description>So this will be a bad change 🙂
I tried to change my old tr/td based blog design to blosxom.php kind div/css
based.
I hope this will be future-aware, I had to work with this for long hours&amp;#8230;
🙂
If you have an idea about how to position the navi div to not to collide with the
main div at bigger font sizes&amp;#8230; Yes, there is font size relative sizing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fortune today</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/fortune-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2004 20:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/fortune-today/</guid>
      <description>I have made a presentation about &amp;#8220;Multimedia on the Macintosh&amp;#8221; on the
DigitalWorld Conference today. I had success, I made a real &amp;#8220;show&amp;#8221; in twenty
minutes (:-P).
Before my presentation there was a drawing, I had luck, maybe first time in
my life :).
I have won a Genius G-Shot P313 camera!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Openoffice.org in a dmg</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/openofficeorg-in-a-dmg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2004 11:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/openofficeorg-in-a-dmg/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I have found the way of doing an OpenOffice.org package, with
just-mount-and-drag-and-drop install. I have still difficulties with the
user directory and the X11 presence, but I will solve it. I had promising meeting with the HDSys (the Hungarian apple distributor), after testing and bugfixes they will probably bundle it for Central European languages.
I have the Hungarian version already working on my desktop 🙂
My next project is to make a Hungarian, tested version of NeoOffice/J, but</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV star: “I&#43;” in FIX.tv</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/tv-star-i-in-fixtv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2004 21:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/tv-star-i-in-fixtv/</guid>
      <description>I will be one of the hosts in i+ (pronounced: Allj meg, means &amp;#8220;stop&amp;#8221;), a new tv
show in fix.tv. The show will show Mac vs. PC fight from one aspect.
And old iMac (base G4 with some extra ram) versus an AMD 2GHz monster. Uh.
This will be a hard fight. We will try to introduce Macintosh for the
public. Fix.tv is a small tv
channel about interactive multimedia and computing, music clips and cars,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle on my Mac</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/oracle-on-my-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2004 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/oracle-on-my-mac/</guid>
      <description>Last week I installed Oracle 9.2 to my PowerBook. I have still problems
setting it up in changing network environment (I have to reedit /etc/hosts
every time I got new IP address) but runs well on my little book. I had to
make an oracle user, with sudo rights&amp;#8230; The tomcat setup has changed
between jaguar and panther, so I had to edit some scripts (allup.sh and
alldown.sh) to make it run properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging in to Mac OS X from modem</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/logging-in-to-mac-os-x-from-modem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2004 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/logging-in-to-mac-os-x-from-modem/</guid>
      <description>I got a support call from my old friend, Meszi. He has a customer who wanted
to use his Mac server from a modem connection. After a sort search I found
mgetty has been ported to Mac OS X. The link is here:
http://www.leo.org/~doering/mgetty/
I had to change Makefile a bit (there is no fax and modem user or group), I
bet nobody will be enough.
On panther I had to remove an &amp;#8220;extern int sys_nerr;&amp;#8221; from the logfile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wannabe Lord of the (snow)boards</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/wannabe-lord-of-the-snowboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2004 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/wannabe-lord-of-the-snowboards/</guid>
      <description>Sunday we will leave for a skying trip, 5 days without Internet access
(Panic! Panic!)&amp;#8230; I think this will be hard. What more, I will have to leave my
PowerBook home 🙁
No way. What will I do in the hospital after breaking my
bones on the slope? 😀 I definitely have to bring the notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almakor MUG meeting last weekend</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/almakor-mug-meeting-last-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2004 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/almakor-mug-meeting-last-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This was such an event! GarageBand demo, beautiful machines&amp;#8230;
aaand&amp;#8230; 512M RAM more in my PowerBook 🙂 I&amp;#8217;m happy with the speedup, but of course I have to
wait for some apps, yet.
I am waiting for G5 notebooks 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Center in Paris</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/apple-center-in-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2004 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/apple-center-in-paris/</guid>
      <description>After some calculations I&amp;#8217;ve decided to buy new battery for my Powerbook here.
I will have problems with warranty but the price was cheaper (around 35
Euros). It&amp;#8217;s hard to find an Apple shop!
I checked apple.fr for the list of resellers, then I met with different
shops:
 They don&amp;#8217;t sell Apple parts but complete computers   They don&amp;#8217;t have stock   The given address is a warehouse (or something with a big steel door)   &amp;#8230; and of course there are others who sell Apple parts 🙂   We&amp;#8217;ve had some problem with France Telecom (their phone boxes are not properly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Paris</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/from-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2004 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/from-paris/</guid>
      <description>Here we are, Sebastien&amp;#8217;s place&amp;#8230; changed a lot&amp;#8230; new furnitures, washing
machine&amp;#8230;
Cool. Today we will try to visit some museums and the Eiffel tower, the
weather is cold but nice.
Today morning I managed to buy some bread and Coke, in French. I&amp;#8217;m proud of
myself 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will be off to Paris</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/will-be-off-to-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2004 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/will-be-off-to-paris/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow evening we will visit Sebastien
(this is a picture, his website is down) in Paris.
This is the first time Maji will join to us, he will be a bit unhappy with the other people speaking foreign languages and no Hungarian. He can understand some basic words and expressions like &amp;#8220;Yes&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;No&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;OK&amp;#8221;, &amp;#8220;Let&amp;#8217;s go&amp;#8221; in English but nothing in French.
We will show him the city, I&amp;#8217;m sure he will enjoy the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimp seminar in NIIF</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/gimp-seminar-in-niif/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2004 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/gimp-seminar-in-niif/</guid>
      <description>Last week I held a seminar about GIMP, within the confines of IPSZILON
project by NIIF. There were a live stream and there will be an archive
some day later.
I had to cut half my planned presentation, because the audience had no idea
about picture formats, colours and other fundamentals, but I think
they were happy with those nifty tricks after the killing theories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord of the Ring 3 – Return of the King</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/lord-of-the-ring-3-return-of-the-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2004 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/lord-of-the-ring-3-return-of-the-king/</guid>
      <description>OK, yesterday evening I managed to collect my friends and buy tickets for
LOTR3. I enjoyed it, the film had outstanding visual effects &amp;#8211; except the
hobbits&amp;#8230; The bluebox stuff was lame and badly lighted. The storyline was
well made, not much quake-like bloodbath&amp;#8230; I think the giant spider was a
bit too scarry. The end was long, but they left out the last boring events
from the book, so it was a bit hollywood-kind end (family, kids, happy wife</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After important exams</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/after-important-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2004 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/after-important-exams/</guid>
      <description>I like it! I have some time today to write a blog entry about my exams and
other things. I did my exams well (I have written a graphics and an applied
informatics exam last week, a numeric recipes exam yesterday), I will have
to make a homework about didactics and I will have a programming languages
exam next week, too. Then two more semesters and I got my MSC!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun with a Powermac G5</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/fun-with-a-powermac-g5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2004 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/fun-with-a-powermac-g5/</guid>
      <description>I borrowed a PowerMac G5 form HAndras, I met him first on a MUG meeting where
I saw his G5 (A clip from HAndras)
He managed to sell his &amp;#8220;old&amp;#8221; 1.6 GHz model and to buy a new one, a freaking
dual 2GHz G5. While the old one is waiting for the new owner HAndras was so
kind he gave it to me to compile the OpenOffice.org.
I am so happy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>