<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>development on Wizguild</title>
    <link>https://wizguild.com/tags/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in development on Wizguild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 11:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wizguild.com/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>iRecipeBook for iPad</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-for-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 11:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/irecipebook-for-ipad/</guid>
      <description>We have a new release! The iPad compatible iRecipeBook was a request, actually we had a bad review, stating that the – iPhone only – iRecipeBook looks wrong on the iPad&amp;#8230; The reviewer stated that five stars will be the award of an iPad compatible release. I&amp;#8217;m waiting!
Meanwhile I&amp;#8217;m already working on localisations, social networking update (Facebook share, Twitter, Pinterest maybe&amp;#8230;) and sharing recipes via email and from within the App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New iRecipeBook release and more</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/new-irecipebook-release-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 11:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/new-irecipebook-release-and-more/</guid>
      <description>iRecipeBook released in App Store just few weeks ago but we already have news about further developments. The new release will support iPad, will have iOS usability and design improvements.
We plan to release it just before Christmas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Magento admin grid without database tables</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/creating-magento-admin-grid-without-database-tables/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 13:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/creating-magento-admin-grid-without-database-tables/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s not common that you have to display something that&amp;#8217;s not in the Magento database. It was not too difficult to figure out how to do it but checking this might save you few minutes.
Feel free to download the code itself: Wizguild_VirtualGrid.zip
 Virtual grid package structure  In the Grid.php I create a Varien_Data_Collection object: protected function _prepareCollection() { $collection = new Varien_Data_Collection(); foreach (array(&#39;alpha&#39;,&#39;beta&#39;,&#39;charlie&#39;) as $item) { $data = new Varien_Object(); $data-&amp;gt;setName($item); $collection-&amp;gt;addItem($data); } $this-&amp;gt;setCollection($collection); } &amp;#8230;then just use it in the _prepareColumns():</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TextWrangler PHPTidy filter</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/textwrangler_phptidy_filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 13:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/textwrangler_phptidy_filter/</guid>
      <description>I love TextWrangler. Performance of TextWrangler is just incredible compared to the alternatives. Just try to open a few hundred megabytes long XML and do a search and replace. Others will give you the spinning beach-ball for minutes. Its only real weakness is long lines. I miss few key features, though. I&amp;#8217;m not a big fan of BBedit, those extra features are not for me, I actually found them very distracting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated iRecipeBook finally</title>
      <link>https://wizguild.com/updated-irecipebook-finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 21:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wizguild.com/updated-irecipebook-finally/</guid>
      <description>It took terribly long to fix the built-in web server. Thank you for your support by using the App and sorry for annoyances. The focus is on social networking features now.
As the database is bigger and bigger, especially after uploading images for every recipe I&amp;#8217;ve realized maybe we will have to implement an option to get rid of big images. The big image feature was introduced to help social networking publication, but clearly we can&amp;#8217;t sacrifice launch performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>